<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Random Thoughts]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Random Thoughts]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/random-thoughts5/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 21:26:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/random-thoughts5/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Caribbean ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Caribbean </h1><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ceb3ef1d-26fb-4164-a773-e2d2ebadacad.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/random-thoughts5/the-caribbean/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7099364d-7612-4b51-be71-28fdd2fb73df</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 21:08:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Love]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Love</h1><p>“...she is the kind of girl you never see coming. It starts simple and a month later you are saying I love you, you are my world. She whispered to me "I want a kiss" and I knew, I was in trouble. I want to spend every night exploring the mystery that is her mind. What is she thinking? What does she want? Is this enough for her? Am I enough for her? Some people you can read like a book, but she is a poem written in another language. Love is never easy to understand. Our love was unexpected, the kind you only read about. One second I was lost in this world, the next I am falling in love. It gives me faith that the world is good. She gives me faith. I look into her eyes and I am in her soul, completely transfixed. She wraps her arms around me and I swear no one has ever felt safer in this world. Fingers intertwined with mine and I am sure we can take on the world. Lying next to her I feel her magic, the kind you can only find in a girl who finds beauty in everything. She kisses me and it takes me to a place where we are together forever. When she laughs, I swear it is the cure for everything. It healed me. She feels like home. No, better than that; she feels like where I belong, where I was always supposed to be. I was not looking for anyone; she showed me my forever. She is the kind of girl that can do that, steal your heart and change your life...”</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/38767b02d04f8e038d1156dec22b147c3fb55e99.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/random-thoughts5/love/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ea55e7e9-dbc6-4c41-9708-043474111afe</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 21:25:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>